export const questionData = [
	{
		question: "What the fuck does .map do?",
		answer: "Iterates over every element of an array in order.",
		// response: true,
	},
	{
		question: "question 2",
		answer: "answer 2",
		// response: true,
	},
	{
		question: "question 3",
		answer: "answer 3",
	},
	{
		question: "question 4",
		answer: "answer 4",
	},
	{
		question: "question 5",
		answer: "answer 5",
	},
	{
		question: "question 6",
		answer: "answer 6",
	},
	{
		question: "question 7",
		answer: "answer 7",
	},
	{
		question: "question 8",
		answer: "answer 8",
	},
	{
		question: "question 9",
		answer: "answer 9",
	},
	{
		question: "question 10",
		answer: "answer 10",
	},
	{
		question: "question 11",
		answer: "answer 11",
	},
	{
		question: "question 12",
		answer: "answer 12",
	},
	{
		question: "question 13",
		answer: "answer 13",
	},
	{
		question: "question 14",
		answer: "answer 14",
	},
	{
		question: "question 15",
		answer: "answer 15",
	},
];
